# Hitarth Bhatt

📳 +91 8302880263 | 💌 hitarthbhatt12@gmail.com | 🖸 github.com/Hitarthbhatt | 🛅 linkedin/hitarth-bhatt

## Personal Profile

1.5+ Years of experience in developing and designing iOS, iPadOS, and watchOS applications. I'm always passionate about developing a fast and reliable application. Throughout my carrier, I've developed applications from scratch to release, Implement enhanced features in big projects.

## Skills\_

**Language & Tools** Swift, C/C++, Xcode, VSCode, SourceTree, Postman, Bagel.

Frameworks & Library SwiftUI, UIKit, Firebase, Combine, Swift Charts, CocoaPods, SPM, JSON, Git.

## Work Experience \_\_\_\_\_

#### **Simform Solutions** (Al-Health App)

Ahmedabad, India

Jul 2021 - Present

iOS Developer

 Working on Fitness application which works over Apple devices (iPad, iPhone, watchOS). Working with 5 person's team in a remote environment and providing fast deliveries of new features.

- Improved legacy code and apply MVVM architecture as well as SwiftUI framework for new features and redesigned screen.
- Refactor more than 40% watchOS screen to SwiftUI framework.
- Implement **pixel-perfect** designs provided by designer.
- Technology Stack: UIKit, SwiftUI, Networking, Concurrency, Firebase, AVFoundation, Swift Charts, etc.

Jain Fast Food (Link)

iOS Developer (Freelance)

Oct 2020 - Mar 2021

- Developed iOS application from scratch and Publish it on App Store.
- Worked with Android developer in sync to manage backend data.
- Developed Admin iOS application which monitors profits, Add and modify the client side app data.
- Used Combine Framework to ensure that the user authenticates perfectly.
- Technology Stack: SwiftUI, Firebase, Push Notification, JSON, SwiftyJSON, Combine, CoreLocation, SDWebImage, etc.

## Projects \_\_\_\_\_

**HyperStock** (Link)

iOS Developer

- · Refactor code performance and fix production code bugs.
- Implement new feature and manage network calling.

**SSLineChart** (Link) Ahmedabad, India

Open Source Project

• SSLineChart draws a **Ulimage** of a chart with given values and provide additional functionality of gradient color fill.

#### **Education**

## Arya College Of Engineering And IT

BTech in Information Technology 2017 - 2021

Govt. Maharawal Se. Sec. School

Senior Secondary Examination (RBSE) 2016 - 2017

Gurukul Se. Sec. Public School

Higher Secondary Examination (RBSE) 2014 - 2015

#### Certificate & Achievements

Present Leetcode, Solved 150+ problems Link

Dec 2019 Udemy, The Complete iOS App Development Bootcamp Link

Oct 2019 University of Toronto, Introduction To Swift Programming

Link